what's up everyone cameras only for five
here with a very special view today
now oh my God
i I don't think I’ve been this excited
to make a video
in like a long at times like I got a
piece of sock
on history in this like oh my God
you're not gonna believe this you're
gonna shake your pants like I'm not even
kidding
doing christmas and like I gotta do
your story first before the grand reveal
my mama she bought me like a bunch of
like shitty presents I was
like no you take all that
back like I don't want it like
like she got me like t-shirts like she
was like she got me toys right I'm
not a baby I want Sonic
Underground I want that su
so you know what she did I made
her
go to ebay and boss you guessed it
the Sonic Underground stickers for like
400 bucks or some I don't know i
don't give a
damn and you know what
i got right here that's right
so I thought you know what but
instead of opening it by myself and
having fun
i thought I would open for my youtube
because you know what
my fans deserve to see this
like at the same time I do is you're
picking
up what I'm putting down
so oh
oh yes oh
i think we need some music up in this
good morning you agree
oh um
this is a piece of sock Underground
history
you seen this yeah your eyes are
deceiving you
i got the official
Sonic auto sticker set from augie donkey
stickers
i got it yeah
hours of creative fun you know I'm gonna
have out of the queer phone now this
like look at that they even got mad at
the Hedgehog
oh you can't make this up
oh my God now granted
one thing that sucks no bottle b
like what what the I mean
i mean I'm not gonna I guess they
thought like knuckle cell
so they put him here even though you
know Knuckles only appeared in like four
while Bobby appears in what what
half that's right I have Bobby's like a
way more popular character but I guess
uh
okey dokey stickers didn't know that
damn
what now what do you say we get this
open because
you all know you want to see me play
with this
i could play with this for hours
holy
I'm trying to be careful because as i
said this is a piece of sock on
history up in this I don't want to
like break it
oh damn
[Music]
oh yes I think I just broke it
damn oh
oh
[Music]
oh yeah that smells like Bobby's
assham all right
or at least what I think it smells like
oni Sonic and smell his ass
oh yes oh yes
look at that oh yes
look at that everyone like reusable
stickers
look at that comes with like like a
background right there too
a background for free
this is insane now i
i want I want to try to keep this
as new looking as possible so I'm going
to take
like the one sticker that I don't care
about
sorry Manic
oh oh oh I got to be careful here
i do not want to these stickers are like
authentic
they are 20 years old I can't stress
that enough
look at that look at that look at that
everyone
look at that
like standing outside my building and
now I don't know
it says these stickers are reusable so i
swear to God
Manic had better not stay up here oh
that looks cool that looks cool
this is awesome
can I take that off it says
reusable
i don't know how I'm gonna do this
oh this does not look reusable
what the how am I supposed to get
off it says the reusable
i gotta get this